#### Contact

smclaughlin2820@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ sharetta-mclaughlin-msn-rnccrn-862aa6150 (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Basic Life Support (BLS)

Cardiology

### Certifications

Critical Care Registered Nurse (Adult) (CCRN-A)

# Sharetta McLaughlin, MSN, RN, CCRN

Master of Science at Holy Family University Greater Philadelphia Area

## Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Inpatient Care, Cardiology, Cath Lab, Healthcare, Basic Life Support (BLS), and Cardiopulmonary Resuscitation (CPR). Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from Thomas Jefferson University.

# Experience

Temple University Hospital Registered Nurse December 2011 - Present (8 years 7 months)

Thomas Jefferson University Hospitals July 2006 - November 2011 (5 years 5 months)

## Education

Holy Family University

Master of Science, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse (2018 - 2020)

Thomas Jefferson University

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2004 - 2006)